

ABDULHAKIM OBSINA

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

As a Software developer, I am a dedicated and enthusiastic professional with a passion for Software development and a strong desire to learn and grow in the field. With a solid foundation in Software development technologies, I possess a strong understanding of Web, Mobile and Desktop applications.

I have experience in developing responsive and user-friendly applications, as well as working with databases and backend technologies.

I am familiar in version control systems like Git and have a good understanding of RESTful APIs.

In addition to my technical skills, I am a proactive problem solver with excellent analytical and troubleshooting abilities. I have a keen eye for detail and take pride in producing clean, efficient, and maintainable code.

I am also a strong collaborator and work well in team environments, contributing ideas and actively participating in discussions.

DOB: May 5, 1999

ABOUT ME



ACADEMIC LEVELDegree Bachelor



GENDER

Male



AGE

23 - 27 Years



WORK EXPERIENCE



FIELD OF STUDY

Computer Science

EDUCATION

CS50 WEB
PROGRAMMING WITH
JAVASCRIPT AND
PYTHON

Harvard university

2024 - Present

I have completed many real life Projects which enhanced my knowledge and expertise towards software development.

BSC IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Hawassa University 2020 - 2023

CGPA:3.37/4.00.

JOB EXPERIENCES

DIGITAL BANKING OFFICER

2023 - Present / Siingee Bank

- -Managed and optimized digital banking platforms to enhance customer experience.
- -Assisted clients with digital banking services, ensuring seamless online transactions.

SOFFTWARE DEVELOPEMENT INTERN

2022 - 2022 / JSI (Jhon Snow inc Ethiopia)

Assisted in the development of new features for the company's main task,

HRIS(human resource information system).

EXPERTISE

Python java programming

javaScript

Django

React js

Angular

LANGUAGES

English Proficient **Amharic**Proficient

Afan Oromo Proficient

Address:

Addis Ababa, Ethiopia, 1000

Phone:

+251972639007

Email:

kimo.obsinal@gmail.com

SKILLS

Philosophy

Software development